Finding Aid for the Paul B. MacCready Papers, 1931-2002 MacCreadyPB
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- AeroVironment, 1
  - Gossamer Condor, 5
    - Gossamer Condor: Award ceremony, 1977; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_06 (Box 1.10, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Condor: autograph book, 1977; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_07 (Box 1.10, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Condor: compilation book, 1977; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_08 (Box 1.10, Folder 8)
    - Gossamer Condor: Smithsonian Institution, National Air and Space Museum, 1977-1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_09 (Box 1.10, Folder 9)
    - Gossamer Condor: draft notes and writings, 1977-1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_10 (Box 1.10, Folder 10)
    - Gossamer Condor: requests for information material, 1977-1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_11 (Box 1.10, Folder 11)
    - Gossamer Condor: Bryan Allen's flight logs, 1977-1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_010_12 (Box 1.10, Folder 12)
    - Gossamer Condor: miscellaneous papers, 1977-1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_01 (Box 1.11, Folder 1)
    - Gossamer Condor: Films, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_02 (Box 1.11, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Condor: information kit and other papers, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_03 (Box 1.11, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Condor: notes about talks and articles, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_04 (Box 1.11, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Condor: Shafter Airport celebrations and administrative papers, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_05 (Box 1.11, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Condor: quotes and poems, 1977-2001; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_06 (Box 1.11, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Condor: World Book-Childcraft International, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_07 (Box 1.11, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Condor: correspondence, folder 2, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_08 (Box 1.11, Folder 8)
    - Gossamer Condor: requests for memorabilia, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_09 (Box 1.11, Folder 9)
    - Gossamer Condor: requests for sets of plans, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_10 (Box 1.11, Folder 10)
    - Gossamer Condor: Bill Rickson, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_11 (Box 1.11, Folder 11)
    - Gossamer Condor: visit to Marengo School, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_12 (Box 1.11, Folder 12)
    - Gossamer Condor: symposium on man-powered flight, 1979 February 7; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_13 (Box 1.11, Folder 13)
    - Gossamer Condor: elementary school material, 1983-1985; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_14 (Box 1.11, Folder 14)
    - Gossamer Condor: visit to Westerly School, 1994; MacCreadyPB_01_05_011_15 (Box 1.11, Folder 15)
    - Drawings
    - Gossamer Condor: Fig. 2 Reduction of first 3-view drawing, 1977 October 9; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_01; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Box 1.12 is a flat box, dimensions 12 x 17 inches
    - Gossamer Condor: Gossamer Condor I (Mojave version), 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_02; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.12, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Condor: Gossamer Condor II, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_03; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.12, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Condor: Gossamer Condor I (Mojave version) and Gossamer Condor II, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_04; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.12, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 1 Propeller, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_05; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 2 Stabilizer, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_06; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 3 Bowsprit Assem., 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_07; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 4 Wing details, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_08; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 8)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 5 Wing layout, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_09; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 9)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 6 Inboard profile, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_10; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 10)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 7 Fuselage structure, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_11; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 11)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 8 Down post and fittings, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_12; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 12)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 9 Fuselage fairings, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_13; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 13)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 10 Fwd fuselage fairing, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_14; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 14)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 11 Prop shaft & sprockets, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_15; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 15)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plan 12 Control system details, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_16; drawing: pencil (Box 1.12, Folder 16)
    - Gossamer Condor: Plans, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_05_012_17; booklet, drawing (Box 1.12, Folder 17)
  - Gossamer Albatross, 6
    - Gossamer Albatross: miscellaneous papers, 1974-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_01 (Box 1.13, Folder 1)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Channel crossing plans and official papers, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_02 (Box 1.13, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Frank J. Malina, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_03 (Box 1.13, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Albatross: contract between P. MacCready and B. Allen, 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_04 (Box 1.13, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Albatross: travel plans and other papers, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_05 (Box 1.13, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Albatross: sponsorship requests and commercial exploitations, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_06 (Box 1.13, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Albatross: design and technical papers, folder 1, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_07 (Box 1.13, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Royal Aeronautical Society, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_08 (Box 1.13, Folder 8)
    - Gossamer Albatross: data book 1, weights, 1978-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_09 (Box 1.13, Folder 9)
    - Gossamer Albatross: data book 3, design, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_10 (Box 1.13, Folder 10)
    - Gossamer Albatross: testing, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_013_11 (Box 1.13, Folder 11)
    - Gossamer Albatross: flight testing conference notes, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_01 (Box 1.14, Folder 1)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Du Pont correspondence, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_02 (Box 1.14, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Du Pont and Gen-Mar, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_03 (Box 1.14, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Albatross: county fairs, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_04 (Box 1.14, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Albatross: press releases, media coverage and other publications, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_05 (Box 1.14, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Albatross: autograph book, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_06 (Box 1.14, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Albatross: weather and tides information, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_014_07 (Box 1.14, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Albatross: congratulatory notes, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_01 (Box 1.15, Folder 1)
    - Gossamer Albatross: information leaflets and other papers, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_02 (Box 1.15, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Thompson Horton Associates, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_03 (Box 1.15, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Albatross: letter from US President Jimmy Carter, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_04 (Box 1.15, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Albatross: design and technical data, folder 2, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_05 (Box 1.15, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Albatross: Glenn H. Bowlus, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_06 (Box 1.15, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Albatross: first-hand account of the Channel crossing by Marshall MacCready, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_07 (Box 1.15, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Albatross: award ceremony and other celebrations, 1979-1980; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_08 (Box 1.15, Folder 8)
    - Gossamer Albatross: correspondence, 1979-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_09 (Box 1.15, Folder 9)
    - Gossamer Albatross: exhibitions displays and correspondence, 1979-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_06_015_10 (Box 1.15, Folder 10)
    - Drawings
    - Gossamer Albatross: drawing, ca. 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_01; drawing: pencil (Box 1.16, Folder 1)
    - Gossamer Albatross: drawing, ca. 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_02; drawing: pencil (Box 1.16, Folder 2)
    - Gossamer Albatross: drawing, ca. 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_03; drawing: pencil (Box 1.16, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Albatross: drawing, ca. 1978; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_04; drawing: pencil (Box 1.16, Folder 4)
    - Gossamer Albatross: drawing, 1978 March 27; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_05; drawing: pencil (Box 1.16, Folder 5)
    - Gossamer Albatross: poster, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_06; print (Box 1.16, Folder 6)
    - Gossamer Albatross, 1979; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_07; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.16, Folder 7)
    - Gossamer Albatross: GA-1 Propeller, 1979 March 9; MacCreadyPB_01_06_016_08; drawing: pen and ink (Box 1.16, Folder 8)
  - Solar powered aircraft, 7
    - Solar aircraft: airfoils, 1976-1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_01 (Box 1.17, Folder 1)
    - Solar aircraft: genesis, 1977-1979; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_02 (Box 1.17, Folder 2)
    - Solar aircraft program: sponsorship requests, 1979-1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_03 (Box 1.17, Folder 3)
    - Gossamer Penguin, 1979-1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_04 (Box 1.17, Folder 4)
    - Solar Albatross, 1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_05 (Box 1.17, Folder 5)
    - Solar Challenger: Astro Flight Inc., 1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_06 (Box 1.17, Folder 6)
    - Solar Challenger: design, 1980; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_07 (Box 1.17, Folder 7)
    - Solar Challenger 1980 and 1981, MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_08 (Box 1.17, Folder 8)
    - Solar aircraft program: reports, costs and papers, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_09 (Box 1.17, Folder 9)
    - Solar Challenger: Pilots, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_10 (Box 1.17, Folder 10)
    - Solar Challenger: financial papers, including agreements with Du Pont and correspondence, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_017_11 (Box 1.17, Folder 11)
    - Solar Challenger: Federal Aviation Administration, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_01 (Box 1.18, Folder 1)
    - Solar Challenger: official papers, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_02 (Box 1.18, Folder 2)
    - Solar Challenger: correspondence, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_03 (Box 1.18, Folder 3)
    - Solar Challenger information pack, 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_04 (Box 1.18, Folder 4)
    - Solar Challenger: Paris to London coordination document, 1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_05 (Box 1.18, Folder 5)
    - Solar Challenger: Tiger Club, 1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_06 (Box 1.18, Folder 6)
    - Solar Challenger: miscellaneous papers, 1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_07 (Box 1.18, Folder 7)
    - Solar Challenger: technical data, flight planning and related papers, 1981; MacCreadyPB_01_07_018_08 (Box 1.18, Folder 8)
    - Drawings
    - Solar Challenger: preliminary design, solar powered aircraft, 1980 May 31; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_01; 1 print: pen and ink drawing (Box 1.19, Folder 1)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 1, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_02; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 2)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 2, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_03; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 3)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 3, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_04; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 4)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 4, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_05; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 5)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 5, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_06; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 6)
    - Solar Challenger: weather drawing 6, 1981 July 7; MacCreadyPB_01_07_019_07; drawing: computer-aided-design (Box 1.19, Folder 7)
  - General Motors including EV1 and GM Sunraycer, 8
    - GM and the International Human Powered Vehicle Association (IHPVA), 1980-1981; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_01 (Box 1.20, Folder 1)
    - GM Sunraycer plan and teams, 1984-1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_02 (Box 1.20, Folder 2)
    - The electrospirit program memo and other papers, 1985; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_03 (Box 1.20, Folder 3)
    - GM and AV relationship discussions and other related documents, 1985-1991; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_04 (Box 1.20, Folder 4)
    - GM Sunraycer: people, 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_05 (Box 1.20, Folder 5)
    - GM Sunraycer strategies, 1987-1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_06 (Box 1.20, Folder 6)
    - GM Sunraycer data, 1987-1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_07 (Box 1.20, Folder 7)
    - GM Sunraycer magazine articles, folder 1, 1987-1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_08 (Box 1.20, Folder 8)
    - GM Sunraycer magazine articles, folder 2, 1987-1989; MacCreadyPB_01_08_020_09 (Box 1.20, Folder 9)
    - GM Sunraycer, Hughes Aircraft, 1987-1989; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_01 (Box 1.21, Folder 1)
    - International Human Powered Vehicle Association (IHPVA), 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_02 (Box 1.21, Folder 2)
    - GM Sunraycer - World Solar Challenge regulations, 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_03 (Box 1.21, Folder 3)
    - GM Sunraycer itinerary maps, 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_04 (Box 1.21, Folder 4)
    - GM Sunraycer press releases, 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_05 (Box 1.21, Folder 5)
    - GM Sunraycer leaflets and brochures, 1987; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_06 (Box 1.21, Folder 6)
    - GM Sunraycer school science education program, 1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_021_07 (Box 1.21, Folder 7)
    - Caltech Ae107 class and Galcit Report 1128, 1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_01 (Box 1.22, Folder 1)
    - GM Sunraycer - Robert Stempel correspondence, 1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_02 (Box 1.22, Folder 2)
    - GM Sunraycer teamwork and technology - for today and tomorrow, 1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_03 (Box 1.22, Folder 3)
    - Tour de Sol race, 1988; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_04 (Box 1.22, Folder 4)
    - GM Sunraycer: miscellaneous papers, 1988-1998; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_05 (Box 1.22, Folder 5)
    - Don Runkle correspondence, 1989-1991; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_06 (Box 1.22, Folder 6)
    - GM Sunraycer dedication to the Smithsonian, 1989 September 28; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_07 (Box 1.22, Folder 7)
    - GM Sunraycer USA, 1990; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_08 (Box 1.22, Folder 8)
    - Electric vehicle plans, 1990; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_09 (Box 1.22, Folder 9)
    - Development of General Motors electric car, 1990; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_10 (Box 1.22, Folder 10)
    - General Motors and Aerovironment agreement, 1990-1991; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_11 (Box 1.22, Folder 11)
    - Autoleap project, 1991; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_12 (Box 1.22, Folder 12)
    - General Motors visit, 1993 December 14-15; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_13 (Box 1.22, Folder 13)
    - AeroVironment and EV manufacturing memo, 1993; MacCreadyPB_01_08_022_14 (Box 1.22, Folder 14)
    - GM technology research partnership directorate, 1993-1994; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_01 (Box 1.23, Folder 1)
    - GM Envisioning Network, 1994; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_02 (Box 1.23, Folder 2)
    - EV material, 1987-1997; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_03 (Box 1.23, Folder 3)
    - Innovation Workshop (GM R and D Center. Warren, MI), 1995 February 16; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_04 (Box 1.23, Folder 4)
    - GM EV1 and the Los Angeles City Council, 1996; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_05 (Box 1.23, Folder 5)
    - Ken Baker, GM Vice-President, correspondence, 1996-1997; MacCreadyPB_01_08_023_06 (Box 1.23, Folder 6)
  - Other AV projects, 9
    - Bionic Bat, 1984; MacCreadyPB_01_09_023_07 (Box 1.23, Folder 7)
    - Quetzalcoatlus Northropi (QN), 1984-1986; MacCreadyPB_01_09_023_08 (Box 1.23, Folder 8)
    - Pathfinder, 1997; MacCreadyPB_01_09_023_09 (Box 1.23, Folder 9)
    - Helios, 2002; MacCreadyPB_01_09_023_10 (Box 1.23, Folder 10)
- Planners and Diaries, 2
  - Diary, 1951; MacCreadyPB_02_00_001_01 (Box 2.1, Folder 1)
  - Diaries, 1954; MacCreadyPB_02_00_001_02 (Box 2.1, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, 1955; MacCreadyPB_02_00_001_03 (Box 2.1, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1956; MacCreadyPB_02_00_001_04 (Box 2.1, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1957; MacCreadyPB_02_00_001_05 (Box 2.1, Folder 5)
  - Diaries, 1958; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_01 (Box 2.2, Folder 1)
  - Diaries, 1959; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_02 (Box 2.2, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, 1960; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_03 (Box 2.2, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1961; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_04 (Box 2.2, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1962; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_05 (Box 2.2, Folder 5)
  - Diaries, 1963; MacCreadyPB_02_00_002_06 (Box 2.2, Folder 6)
  - Diaries, 1964; MacCreadyPB_02_00_003_01 (Box 2.3, Folder 1)
  - Diaries, 1965; MacCreadyPB_02_00_003_02 (Box 2.3, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, 1966; MacCreadyPB_02_00_003_03 (Box 2.3, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1967; MacCreadyPB_02_00_003_04 (Box 2.3, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1968; MacCreadyPB_02_00_003_05 (Box 2.3, Folder 5)
  - Diaries, 1969; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_01 (Box 2.4, Folder 1)
  - Diaries, 1970; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_02 (Box 2.4, Folder 2)
  - Diaries, 1971; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_03 (Box 2.4, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1972; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_04 (Box 2.4, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1973-1974; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_05 (Box 2.4, Folder 5)
  - Appointment calendars and address book, 1962; 1969-1974; 1999; MacCreadyPB_02_00_004_06 (Box 2.4, Folder 6)
- Notebooks, 3
  - Black notebook no. 1, October 1961-March 1962; MacCreadyPB_03_00_001_01 (Box 3.1, Folder 1)
  - Black notebook no. 2, April-December 1962; MacCreadyPB_03_00_001_02 (Box 3.1, Folder 2)
  - Black notebook no. 3, February-November 1964; MacCreadyPB_03_00_001_03 (Box 3.1, Folder 3)
  - Black notebook no. 4, December 1964-July 9, 1965; MacCreadyPB_03_00_001_04 (Box 3.1, Folder 4)
  - Black notebook no. 5, July 10, 1965-January 27, 1966; MacCreadyPB_03_00_001_05 (Box 3.1, Folder 5)
  - Black notebook no. 6, January 27, 1966-July 15, 1966; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_01 (Box 3.2, Folder 1)
  - Black notebook [no. 7], August 17, 1966-February 6, 1967; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_02 (Box 3.2, Folder 2)
  - Black notebook [no. 8], January 25, -August 29, 1967; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_03 (Box 3.2, Folder 3)
  - Black notebook [no. 9], August 17, 1967-March 22, 1968; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_04 (Box 3.2, Folder 4)
  - Black notebook [no. 10], March 29, 1968-December 11, 1968, January 9, 1969; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_05 (Box 3.2, Folder 5)
  - Black notebook [no. 11], December16, 1968- June 26, 1969; MacCreadyPB_03_00_002_06 (Box 3.2, Folder 6)
  - Black notebook [no. 12], July 7, 1969-March 3, 1970; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_01 (Box 3.3, Folder 1)
  - Black notebook [no. 13], March 3-August 25, 1970; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_02 (Box 3.3, Folder 2)
  - Black notebook [no. 14], December 15, 1970-May 28, 1971; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_03 (Box 3.3, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 1], June 1-August 10, 1971; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_04 (Box 3.3, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 2], August 10-October 5, 1971; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_05 (Box 3.3, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 3], October 6-November 26, 1971; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_06 (Box 3.3, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no. 4], November 22, 1971-January 22, 1972; MacCreadyPB_03_00_003_07 (Box 3.3, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 5], February 19-May 25, 1972; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_01 (Box 3.4, Folder 1)
  - Blue notebook [no. 6], December 20-21, 1971, April 27-June 26, 1972; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_02 (Box 3.4, Folder 2)
  - Blue notebook [no. 7], September 6-December 22, 1972; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_03 (Box 3.4, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 8], January 3-May 22, 1973; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_04 (Box 3.4, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 9], June 18-December 13, 1973; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_05 (Box 3.4, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 10], December 14, 1973-May 31, 1974; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_06 (Box 3.4, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no.11], May 30-September 5, 1974; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_07 (Box 3.4, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 12], September 7-December 2, 1974; MacCreadyPB_03_00_004_08 (Box 3.4, Folder 8)
  - Blue notebook [no. 13], December 5, 1974-February 9, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_01 (Box 3.5, Folder 1)
  - Blue notebook [no. 14], February 24-April 25, 1975, May 16, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_02 (Box 3.5, Folder 2)
  - Blue notebook [no. 15], April 25-May 24, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_03 (Box 3.5, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 16], June 11-July 27, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_04 (Box 3.5, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 17], July 28-September 25, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_05 (Box 3.5, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 18], September 24-November 21, 1975; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_06 (Box 3.5, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no. 19], November 21, 1975-February 3, 1976; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_07 (Box 3.5, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 17], February 4-June 1, 1976; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_08 (Box 3.5, Folder 8)
  - Blue notebook [no. 18], June 2-September 9, 1976; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_09 (Box 3.5, Folder 9)
  - Blue notebook [no. 19], September 10-November 11, 1976; MacCreadyPB_03_00_005_10 (Box 3.5, Folder 10)
  - Blue notebook [no. 23], November 12, 1976-February 7, 1977; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_01 (Box 3.6, Folder 1)
  - Blue notebook [no. 24], February 2-April 11, 1977; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_02 (Box 3.6, Folder 2)
  - Blue notebook [no. 25], April 11-June 24, 1977; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_03 (Box 3.6, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 26], June 24-August 31, 1977; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_04 (Box 3.6, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 27], August 31-October 28, 1977; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_05 (Box 3.6, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 28], October 28, 1977-January 16, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_06 (Box 3.6, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no. 29], January 16-March 17, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_07 (Box 3.6, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 30], March 20-May 17, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_08 (Box 3.6, Folder 8)
  - Blue notebook [no. 31], May 18-July 7, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_09 (Box 3.6, Folder 9)
  - Blue notebook [no. 32], June 23-August 28, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_10 (Box 3.6, Folder 10)
  - Blue notebook [no. 33], August 15-November 17, 1978; MacCreadyPB_03_00_006_11 (Box 3.6, Folder 11)
  - Blue notebook [no. 34], November 17, 1978-February 6, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_01 (Box 3.7, Folder 1)
  - Blue notebook [no. 35], February 7-April 18, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_02 (Box 3.7, Folder 2)
  - Blue notebook [no. 36], April 18-June 11, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_03 (Box 3.7, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 37], June 11-July 26, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_04 (Box 3.7, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 38], July 27-September 19, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_05 (Box 3.7, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 39], September 19-October 13, 1979; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_06 (Box 3.7, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no. 40], November 26, 1979-February 9, 1980; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_07 (Box 3.7, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 41], February 8-April 15, 1980; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_08 (Box 3.7, Folder 8)
  - Blue notebook [no. 42], April 10-July 15, 1980; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_09 (Box 3.7, Folder 9)
  - Blue notebook [no. 43], July 14-October 1, 1980; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_10 (Box 3.7, Folder 10)
  - Blue notebook [no. 44], October 1, 1980-January 7, 1981; MacCreadyPB_03_00_007_11 (Box 3.7, Folder 11)
  - Blue notebook [no. 45], January 7-April 3, 1981; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_01 (Box 3.8, Folder 1)
  - Blue notebook [no. 46], April 4-June 9, 1981; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_02 (Box 3.8, Folder 2)
  - Blue notebook [no. 47], June 5-August 4, 1981; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_03 (Box 3.8, Folder 3)
  - Blue notebook [no. 48], August 4-October 23, 1981; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_04 (Box 3.8, Folder 4)
  - Blue notebook [no. 49], October 23, 1981-January 28, 1982; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_05 (Box 3.8, Folder 5)
  - Blue notebook [no. 50], January 28-April 30, 1982; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_06 (Box 3.8, Folder 6)
  - Blue notebook [no. 51], May 1-July 31, 1982; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_07 (Box 3.8, Folder 7)
  - Blue notebook [no. 52], August 1-October 10, 1982; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_08 (Box 3.8, Folder 8)
  - Blue notebook [no. 53], October 12, 1982-January 14, 1983; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_09 (Box 3.8, Folder 9)
  - Blue notebook [no. 54], January 15-April 21, 1983; MacCreadyPB_03_00_008_10 (Box 3.8, Folder 10)